EVGENIY SULIM



Contacts

github.com/evgeniy210191

bees127@ukr.net

 bees127@ukr.net

bees127@ukr.net

 bees127@ukr.net

 bees127@ukr.n

> +38 (066) 923 16 38

Languages

Ukrainian

Russian

English (A0)

Summary

Hello, I'm Eugene, I'm 32 years old, I'm disabled. I want to become an IT professional. Now I am looking for a company that will help me in my professional growth and open up opportunities for me to develop in this area. In turn, I guarantee reliable, long-term cooperation with high returns and focus on results. Yes, I do not have much practical experience and I do not know much, but I am ready to work, learn and develop for the benefit of the company (and mine).

Skills

HTML SASS JavaScript (in the process of studying) CSS

webpack

Git adaptive site

Experience

eleksacademy March 2022 - July 2022

Ukrainian it-scool January 2022 - present

January 2023 - present

Education

Kharkiv National University of Construction and Architecture, faculty of Sanitary Engineering, specialty - heat and gas supply and ventilation, 2013